Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - Hawaii
    - Honolulu
      - Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1973 (Box 151, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 151)
    - Publicity, 1964-1969 (Box 151, Folder 46)
    - Honolulu, Watumull Foundation, 1962-1969 (Box 151, Folder 47)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Reports, 1965-1971 (Box 151, Folder 48)
  - Idaho
    - Anti-Poverty, 1971 (Box 151, Folder 49)
    - Contacts, 1963-1974 (Box 151, Folder 50)
    - Hospitals, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 51)
    - Legal, 1919-1972 (Box 151, Folder 52)
    - Migrants, 1968-1970 (Box 151, Folder 53)
    - Public Health, 1962-1977 (Box 151, Folder 54)
    - Public Welfare, 1969 (Box 151, Folder 55)
    - Schools, General, 1969 (Box 151, Folder 56)
    - Boise
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1971
        - 1973-1974 (Box 151, Folder 57)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 151)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 151, Folder 58)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 151)
      - PP of Idaho
        - 1971-1974 (Box 151, Folder 59)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 151)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 151, Folder 60)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 151)
      - Field Visit from 1969
        - 1969-1971 (Box 151, Folder 61)
        - 1978 (Box 151)
  - Illinois
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1971 (Box 151, Folder 62)
    - Department of HEW, Region V, 1970
      - 1970-1974 (Box 151, Folder 63)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 151)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1963-1974 (Box 151, Folder 64)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 151)
    - Illinois Family Planning Council, Inc. from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 151, Folder 65)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 151)
    - Family Planning, Coordinating Council, 1971-1972 (Box 151, Folder 66)
    - Hospital, General, 1964-1971 (Box 151, Folder 67)
    - Hospitals, Cook County Hospital Situation, 1958-1966 (Box 151, Folder 68)
    - Legal, 1937-1970 (Box 151, Folder 69)
    - Migrant, 1964-1969 (Box 151, Folder 70)
    - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 151, Folder 71)
    - Publicity, Public Welfare, 1962-1965 (Box 151, Folder 72)
    - Public Health, Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 151, Folder 73)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 151, Folder 74)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1967-1969 (Box 151, Folder 75)
    - Schools, General from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - 1977 (Box 152)
    - University of Chicago
      - Schools, General, Correspondence from 1964
        - 1963-1973 (Box 152, Folder 2)
        - 1978 (Box 152)
      - 4th Workshop, Mass Communication, 1965-1968 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - 3rd Workshop, Mass Communication, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - 2nd Workshop, Mass Communication, 1964 (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - 1st Workshop, Mass Communications, 1961-1963 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Mass Communication, Reports, 1955-1964 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Schools, Dr. Philip Hauser, 1964-1968 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - University of Illinois, Schools from 1965
      - 1965-1969 (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - 1979 (Box 152)
    - Chicago, Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1965 (Box 152, Folder 10-13)
    - Bloomington
      - PP of Mid Central Illinois (formerly McLean County), 1970-1972 (Box 152, Folder 14)
      - Affiliation, Normal Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 152, Folder 15)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 152)
      - Affiliation, PP of Mid Central Illinois (formerly McLean County) from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 152, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 152)
      - PP of Mid Central Illinois, Inc. (formerly McLean County), Reports, Members from 1970
        - 1973 (Box 152, Folder 17)
        - 1979 (Box 152)
    - Carbondale, PP, 1957-1967 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Champaign County
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1946
        - 1946-1973 (Box 152, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 152)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1958
        - 1958-1974 (Box 152, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 152)
      - PP Association of Champaign County, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 152, Folder 21)
      - PP Association from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 152, Folder 22)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 152)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 23)
      - PP Association, Reports, General from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 152, Folder 24)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 152)
      - PP Association, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., undated (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - Chicago
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1972 (Box 152, Folder 26)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 152)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 152, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 152)
      - PP Association, Chicago Area from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 152, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 152)
      - PP Association, 1968 (Box 152, Folder 29)
      - Chicago Area, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 30)
      - Chicago Area PP Association, 1965-1966 (Box 152, Folder 31)
      - Chicago Area PP Association, 1960-1964 (Box 152, Folder 32)
      - PP Association Chicago Area, Field Visit Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 152, Folder 33)
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1964-1968 (Box 152, Folder 34)
    - Champaign, Field Trips, 1950-1962 (Box 152, Folder 35)
    - Chicago
      - PP Association, 1969 (Box 152, Folder 36)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 152, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 152)
    - Illinois PP Council
      - 1974 (Box 152, Folder 38)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 152)
    - Chicago Area
      - Chicago PP Association, Public Affairs, undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - PP Association, Reports, General from 1964
        - 1964-1967 (Box 153, Folder 2)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 153)
      - PP Association, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1972-1976 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - Workshops, Uniform Accounting, 9/28-29/1967 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - PP Association, Field Trips, 1960-1966 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Danville
      - Affiliation, PP Association of Vermillion County, 1948-1956 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      - Field Trips, 1950-1955 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Decatur
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1972 (Box 153, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 153, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
      - PP Steering Committee from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 153, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 153)
      - PP OD Decatur, Inc., Reports, Members from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 153, Folder 11)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 153)
    - East St. Louis, PP, 1965 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Peoria
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 153, Folder 13)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1967
        - 1966-1974 (Box 153, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
      - PP Association from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 153, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
      - Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 153, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1969 (Box 153, Folder 17)
      - Rockford, PP, 1965-1968 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Springfield
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1973
        - 1972-1974 (Box 153, Folder 19)
        - 1978-1980 (Box 153)
      - Affiliation, PP Springfield Area, Correspondence from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 153, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
      - PP Springfield Area from 1973
        - 1972-1974 (Box 153, Folder 21)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
      - PP Springfield Area, Reports, Members, 1975-1976 (Box 153, Folder 22)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of Springfield, 1949-1965 (Box 153, Folder 23)
      - PP Association of Springfield, 1959-1965 (Box 153, Folder 24)
      - Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 153, Folder 25)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1960 (Box 153, Folder 26)
      - General, Field Trips, 1949-1952 (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - Chicago
      - Newspaper Articles
        - 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 153, Folder 28-30)
      - Editorials, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 31)
      - Newspapers, 1962-1963 (Box 153, Folder 32-34)
      - Cook County 1963-1964 (Box 153, Folder 35)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 153, Folder 36-37)
    - Newspaper Clips, 1962-1966 (Box 153, Folder 38)
    - Public Health, 1963-1965 (Box 153, Folder 39)
  - Indiana
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1969 (Box 153, Folder 40)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1965-1974 (Box 153, Folder 41)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
    - Indiana Family Planning Project from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 153, Folder 42)
      - 1975 (Box 153)
    - Hospitals, 1970-1971 (Box 153, Folder 43)
    - Legal from 1922
      - 1922-1966 (Box 153, Folder 44)
      - 1975 (Box 153)
    - Medical Society, 1929-1962 (Box 153, Folder 45)
    - Migrant, 1959-1968 (Box 153, Folder 46)
    - Public Health, 1964-1973 (Box 153, Folder 47)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 153, Folder 48)
    - United Fund, 1965-1970 (Box 153, Folder 49)
    - United Way, 1977 (Box 153, Folder 50)
    - Schools, General, 1964-1974 (Box 153, Folder 51)
    - Schools, Indiana University, 1964-1975 (Box 153, Folder 52)
    - Indiana PP Affiliates Association from 1974
      - 1944 (Box 153, Folder 53)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
    - Indiana PP Affiliates Association, Field Visit Report, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 54)
    - Anderson
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1968-1972 (Box 153, Folder 55)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 153, Folder 56)
      - PP, 1966-1970 (Box 153, Folder 57)
      - Reports, Members, 1969-1973 (Box 153, Folder 58)
    - Bloomington
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 153, Folder 59)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1963
        - 1964-1974 (Box 153, Folder 60)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 153)
      - PP of South Central Indiana, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 153, Folder 61)
      - General South Central Indiana Reports, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 62)
      - PP of South Central Indiana, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 153, Folder 63)
      - PP Committee from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 153, Folder 64)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
      - PP of South Central Indiana, Field Visit Reports, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 65)
      - Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1964-1970 (Box 153, Folder 66)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 153)
      - PP South Central Indiana, Inc., Grant Application, 1975-1976 (Box 153, Folder 67)
    - Evansville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1972 (Box 153, Folder 68)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 153)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1951
        - 1951-1974 (Box 153, Folder 69)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 153)
      - Planned Parenthood from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 153, Folder 70)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 153)
      - Mideast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1965 (Box 153, Folder 71)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1960 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, Mead Johnson Research Center, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - PP League, Reports, General from 1956
        - 1963-1966 (Box 154, Folder 3)
        - 1977 (Box 154)
      - PP League, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 154, Folder 4)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 154)
      - PP, Publicity, 1962-1972 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Fort Wayne
      - PP of Northeastern Indiana, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - PP Northeastern Indiana, 1977-1979 (Box 154, Folder 9)
      - Affiliation, PP Committee, 1949-1953 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Indianapolis, Field Trips, 1952-1960 (Box 154, Folder 11)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1946
        - 1949-1973 (Box 154, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1951
        - 1951-1974 (Box 154, Folder 13)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
      - PP Association from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 154, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 154)
      - Reports, Members from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 154, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
      - PP Association, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1951-1959 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Lafayette
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1965-1972 (Box 154, Folder 17)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 154, Folder 18)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
      - PP Association of Tippecanoe County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 154, Folder 19)
      - Tecumseh Area PP Association, Inc. (formerly PP Association of Tippecanoe) from 1966
        - 1965-1974 (Box 154, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - Reports, General, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 21)
      - Reports, Members from 1967
        - 1967-1971 (Box 154, Folder 22)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 154)
    - Merrillville (formerly in Gary)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 154, Folder 23)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP of Northwest Indiana, Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 154, Folder 24)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - PP Association of Northwest Indiana, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 25)
      - PP Northwest Indiana, Legal, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 154, Folder 26)
      - PP of Northwest Indiana from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 154, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
    - Gary (Merrillville)
      - PP Association Lake County, 1966-1969 (Box 154, Folder 28)
      - PP Association Lake County, 1964-1965 (Box 154, Folder 29)
      - Field Trips, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 30)
      - Merrillville PP, Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 154, Folder 31)
      - Merrillville PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 154, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
    - Muncie
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 154, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 154, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - PP of East Central Indiana, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 154, Folder 35)
      - PP of Delaware County from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 154, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 154)
      - Merger: PP Delaware County, Muncie; PP Madison County, Anderson, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 37)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1969 (Box 154, Folder 38)
      - Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1973 (Box 154, Folder 39)
        - 1976 (Box 154)
    - South Bend
      - PP North Central Indiana, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 154, Folder 40)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1968-1974 (Box 154, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1965
        - 1967-1974 (Box 154, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - PP of North Central Indiana, Inc. from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 154, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 154, Folder 44)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
      - PP of North Central Indiana, Inc., Publicity, 1978 (Box 154, Folder 45)
      - Field Trips, 1948-1954 (Box 154, Folder 46)
    - Terre Haute
      - Affiliates, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 47)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP Vigo County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 154, Folder 48)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 154)
      - PP Association of Wabash Valley, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 154, Folder 49)
      - from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 154, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 154)
      - PP of Vigo County, Chapters from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 154, Folder 51)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 154)
      - Reports, Members from 1970
        - 1970 (Box 154, Folder 52)
        - 1976 (Box 154)
  - Iowa
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1969 (Box 154, Folder 53)
    - Contacts from 1956
      - 1965-1974 (Box 154, Folder 54)
      - 1976-1979 (Box 154)
    - Hospitals, General, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 55)
    - Legal,1939-1974 (Box 154, Folder 56)
    - Migrant, 1966-1971 (Box 154, Folder 57)
    - Public Health from 1962
      - 1962-1968 (Box 154, Folder 58)
      - 1976 (Box 154)
    - Public Welfare, 1960-1969 (Box 154, Folder 59)
    - United Fund, 1967-1970 (Box 154, Folder 60)
    - Schools, General, 1962-1971 (Box 154, Folder 61)
    - Iowa State University, 1963-1972 (Box 154, Folder 62)
    - IPPAC: Iowa Planned Parenthood Affiliates' Council, 1976-1980 (Box 154, Folder 63)
    - Iowa Statewide PP Meeting, Correspondence 10/19/1972 (Box 154, Folder 64)
    - Cedar Rapids
      - PP Council of Cedar Rapids from 1951 (closed 1958), 1951-1958 (Box 154, Folder 65)
      - Field Trips, 1955-1956 (Box 154, Folder 66)
      - Affiliation, PP of Linn County, 1979-1980 (Box 154, Folder 67)
      - PP of Linn County, 1979 (Box 154, Folder 68)
      - PP of Linn County, Reports, Members, 1979 (Box 154, Folder 69)
    - Des Moines
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1943
        - 1943-1974 (Box 154, Folder 70)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1958
        - 1958-1974 (Box 154, Folder 71)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 154)
      - PP of Iowa, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 72)
      - Planned Parenthood of Iowa, 1975-1979 (Box 154, Folder 73)
      - PP of Iowa, 1970-1974 (Box 154, Folder 74)
      - PP, 1968-1969 (Box 154, Folder 75)
      - PP, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 76)
      - PP, 1963-1966 (Box 154, Folder 77)
      - PP of Iowa, Chapters from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 154, Folder 78)
        - 1975 (Box 154)
      - "The Societal Cost and Savings Made Possible by PP of Iowa," Schmautz, E.N. (Thesis, Drake University), 1966 (Box 154, Folder 79)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1962 (Box 154, Folder 80)
      - "Master Plan," Compiled for PP of Iowa by Robert Carlson, Project Developer, 1968 (Box 154, Folder 81)
      - Reports, Clinics,1967-1969 (Box 154, Folder 82)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1970 (Box 154, Folder 83)
      - Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 154, Folder 84)
        - 1975 (Box 154)
      - PP, Publicity, 1963-1969 (Box 154, Folder 85)
    - Mt. Pleasant (formerly Keokuk)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1973
        - 1972 (Box 154, Folder 86)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 154)
      - Affiliation, PP of Southeast Iowa, Correspondence from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 154, Folder 87)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 154)
      - PP of Southeast Iowa, 1976-1979 (Box 154, Folder 88)
    - Keokuk, Planned Parenthood from 1967
      - 1967-1974 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - 1975 (Box 155)
    - Mt. Pleasant (formerly Keokuk)
      - PP Southeast Iowa, Chapters, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      - PP Southeast Iowa, Reports, Members, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Sioux City
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1973 (Box 155, Folder 4)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 155)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957
        - 1957-1973 (Box 155, Folder 5)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
      - PP from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 155, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 7)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 155, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 155)
      - PP, Publicity, 1963-1968 (Box 155, Folder 9)
      - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1970 (Box 155, Folder 10)
      - Field Trips, 1955-1964 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Waterloo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1975-1977 (Box 155, Folder 12)
      - Affiliation, PP of Northeast Iowa, Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 155, Folder 13)
      - PP of Northeast Iowa, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Kansas
    - Anti-Poverty, 1968-1971 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 155, Folder 16)
      - 1978 (Box 155)
    - Hospitals, General, 1967-1972 (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Junior League, 1970-1971 (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Legal, 1963-1971 (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Migrant, 1967-1969 (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Problem Pregnancy Counseling Service, Temporary Folder, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Public Health, 1963-1974 (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Public Welfare, 1963-1970 (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Kansas State Maternal and Child Health and Family Planning Program, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - United Fund, 1968 (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Family Planning Workshop, Dodge City, Kansas, 4/6/1970 (Box 155, Folder 27)
    - Schools, General, 1967-1972 (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - Kansas State University, Home Economist Seminar, Family Planning, 6/28-7/22 1971 (Box 155, Folder 29)
    - University of Kansas Med Center, 1964-1974 (Box 155, Folder 30)
    - Wichita
      - Field Trips, 1958 (Box 155, Folder 31)
      - Affiliation, PP of Kansas, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 155, Folder 32)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 155, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 155)
      - Affiliation, PP of Kansas, Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 155, Folder 34)
      - Affiliation, PP South Central Kansas, Correspondence from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 155, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
      - PP of Kansas, 1977-1979 (Box 155, Folder 36)
      - PP South Central Kansas from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 155, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 155)
      - PP South Central, Planning Workshop, 1/11-12/74, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 38)
      - PP of Kansas, Hays Chapter, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 39)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1972 (Box 155, Folder 40)
      - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966-1968 (Box 155, Folder 41)
  - Kentucky
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips from 1964, undated (Box 155, Folder 42)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1969 (Box 155, Folder 43)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1965-1971 (Box 155, Folder 44)
      - 1976 (Box 155)
    - Hospitals, General, 1964-1973 (Box 155, Folder 45)
    - Legal, Correspondence, 1936-1958 (Box 155, Folder 46)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 155, Folder 47)
    - Public Health, Correspondence from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 155, Folder 48)
      - 1975 (Box 155)
    - Public Health, Family Planning Institute, 3/29-30/64, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 49)
    - Public Welfare, 1949-1968 (Box 155, Folder 50)
    - Schools, General, 1965-1972 (Box 155, Folder 51)
    - University of, 1963-1968 (Box 155, Folder 52)
    - Kentucky PP Affiliates, Committee, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 53)
    - Berea
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1956
        - 1956-1972 (Box 155, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 155)
      - Affiliation, PP, Mountain Maternal League, Correspondence from 1954
        - 1954-1972 (Box 155, Folder 55)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 155)
      - Mountain Maternal Health League, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 155, Folder 56)
      - PP, Mountain Maternal Health League from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 155, Folder 57)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
      - Mountain Maternal Health League, Reports, General, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 58)
      - Mountain Maternal Health League, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 155, Folder 59)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 155)